http://www.epigee.org/policy.html

Privacy Policy
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use and Disclaimer, Epigee.org collects certain information about you that you specifically and knowingly provide to us, such as your user name, email address, name or mailing address. In addition, we may track how you use this Site and relate it to the information you have provided to us. If you wish to be notified of the use of such tracking software and/or disable such software, your browser may offer this feature by means of its options or preferences menu.
The above-described information (Personally-Identifying Information) may be used by Epigee.org to personalize and enhance your use of this Site, including the marketing and promotion of certain products and services that might be of interest to you. Your use of this Site is a consent to the foregoing use of your Personally-Identifying Information by Epigee.org.
Epigee.org also may share your Personally-Identifying Information with select companies and organizations for their own marketing and promotional use. While Epigee.org seeks to share Personally-Identifying Information with companies that follow appropriate privacy policies, it does not bear any responsibility for the actions and policies of such third parties. If you wish that we not share your Personally-Identifying Information with third parties, you may "opt out" by emailing us with such request.
You should be aware that any Personally-Identifying Information, such as your user name and email address, as well as any other information that you post on a bulletin board, share in a "chat room," or otherwise specifically and knowingly disclose by use of the Forums, may be directly collected and used by third parties. Therefore, you may be subject to unsolicited email as a result of your disclosure of such information. You should have no expectation of privacy with respect to your communications through the forums.
Terms of Use and Disclaimer
Usage of this Site is subject to the following terms and conditions:
The information appearing on Epigee.org is presented for educational purposes only. While the information published on this site is believed to be accurate, it is not intended to substitute for professional medical advice. If you have questions or concerns regarding your physical or mental health or the health your baby, please seek assistance from a qualified healthcare provider.
Statements and opinions expressed in our articles and elsewhere on this site are not necessarily those of Epigee.org and should not be considered facts. Epigee.org offers this site and the information contained herein without any warranty of any kind, express or implied, and is not liable for its accuracy, for mistakes, errors, or omissions of any kind, nor for any loss or damage caused by a user's reliance on information obtained from the site.
Epigee.org and its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, partners, employees and independent contractors make no representations regarding the information and materials provided on this web site. All information, software, products, services and links to other web sites are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind, including implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. In no event shall Epigee.org be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special or consequential damages arising out of or connected in any way with the use of, or inability to use, any material on this web site even if Epigee.org publishing has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
The articles on this site are meant to answer questions of a general nature regarding issues of interest to women's reproductive health. If you have a specific medical concern, please contact your healthcare provider. Articles by the Epigee.org Expert Panelists do not necessarily represent the opinions and ideas of Epigee.org. Neither the Expert Panelists, Epigee.org nor Epigee.org guarantee the accuracy or completeness of any information contained in these articles and neither Epigee.org, Epigee.org. nor the Expert Panelist is responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information, nor shall be liable or responsible to any person or entity for any loss or damage caused, or alleged to have been caused, directly or indirectly by the information or ideas referenced or suggested on this site.
Epigee.org has the right to publish, edit or reject any and all submissions via this site, including your name and e-mail address as provided by you, online and in our print publications. Epigee.org offers these bulletin boards and the information contained herein without warranty, express or implied, and accepts no responsibility for the accuracy of the material presented herein or any errors or omissions.
We expect our guests to abide by common standards of decency, and no commercial advertisements are allowed without express permission of Epigee.org.
Your Privacy
By uploading files or data onto the site, or otherwise providing information on or through the site (each, a "submission"), you are granting Epigee.org. a royalty-free, perpetual, non-exclusive, worldwide license to: use, copy, adapt, transmit, publicly perform, display or distribute the submission, without limitation.
Your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of these terms and conditions of use as well as our Privacy Policy and waiver of liability on the part of Epigee.org.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here http://www.networkadvertising.org.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org.
We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Additional Information
The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.
Google, as a third party vendor,
uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie
enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites
and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use
of the DART cookie by visiting the Google
ad and content network privacy policy.
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here
Login to comment
Log in or sign up
Username:
Password:
CANCEL
(0 Comments)
Login to add a comment
Post a comment
You must be logged in to comment.
Copyright© 2020 epigee.org. All rights reserved.
Contact Us | About Us | Privacy Policy
| Library | Epigee Pregnancy and Women's Health
